Kuan-Hung Yeh

https://peterntuph.github.io/

PROFILE

I am currently a graduate from Department of Public Health, National Taiwan University. With the goal of reducing health inequality, my research interests focus on development and application of causal inference methods to estimate causal effect on risk factors and health outcomes using genetic variant. B05801047@ntu.edu.tw +886-956073355

7F., No. 536, Linsen N. Rd., Zhongshan Dist., Taipei City Taiwan (R.O.C.)

RESEARCH EXPERIENCE

Taiwan Public Health Association | Jul.2020 – Present Research Assistant | *Advisor: <u>Tzu-Pin Lu</u>* & <u>Hsien-Ho Lin</u>

 Conducted research on "Post-pandemic lifestyle behavior monitoring on automatic mask detection" authorized by Taiwan Centers for Disease Control (CDC).

Biostatistics & Bioinformatics lab, NTU | Jun.2019 – Feb.2020 Undergraduate Researcher | *Advisor: <u>Tzu-Pin Lu</u>*

- Constructed a prognostic model typically for Asian colon cancer patients with Harrell c-index near 0.75.
- **Poster presentation** in 2019 Taiwan Public Health Joint Annual Conference. [Poster Link]
- Won **Best Topic Research Poster Award** in CPH, NTU.
- Granted by College Student Research Scholarship, Ministry of Science and Technology, Taiwan.
- Under review by the **European Journal of Epidemiology**.

Dept of Medical Research, TVGH | Jun.2019 – Aug.2019 Research Intern | *Advisor: Tzu-Hung Hsiao*

- Detected susceptibility loci associated with metabolic syndrome for subjects with abdominal obesity. [Poster Link]
- Under review by 2020 IEEE International Conference on Bioinformatics and Biomedicine (IEEE BIBM 2020)

Inst of Information Science, Academia Sinica | Summer.2018
Summer Research Intern and Assistant | Advisor: Da-Wei Wang

 Built Diagnosis Related Groups (DRGs) on Ophthalmology by using machine learning algorithms. [Github Link]

EDUCATION

National Taiwan University

Bachelor of Science, Public Health

Major: Biostatistics

Infectious Diseases

Cumulative GPA: 3.75/4.0 (WES)

LANGUAGE

Advanced Proficiency in English

GRE (2019,12)

Verbal: 152 (54th Percentile)

Quantitative: 167 (89th Percentile)

Analytical Writing: 3.0

TOEFL (2020,09)

Reading: 29 Speaking: 22 Listening: 28 Writing: 21

Total: 100

Native Proficiency in Mandarin Basic Proficiency in Japanese

SKILLS

Statistical Tools:

R Language (Proficient) SAS (Basic), SQL(Basic)

Programming:

Python (Proficient) Markdown (Basic)

COMPETITIONS

2018 TMU x MIT (Sana) HIOT Hackathon | Oct.2018

1st Prize with NT\$80,000 (out of 20 teams) [News Link]

- A hackathon organized by Taipei Medical University and MIT Sana Global Team, Boston.
- Proposed an Ultrasound Assisting System for examination of internal hemorrhage with 93% accuracy rate.

2018 Hack x Heart | Sep.2018

Top 12 teams (out of 60 teams)

- A hackathon organized by Taiwan Heart Foundation and Ministry of Science and Technology.
- Built an app to increase medication adherence among patient with acute coronary syndrome.
- Won Innovation Award from Xin Chen Medical Research Foundation and School of Pharmacy, NTU.

ACTIVITIES

29th Health Services & Dedication Award | *Volunteer Investigator* **Highest official award for medical personnel in TAIWAN(R.O.C.)**

Aug.2019

- Represented the Legislative Yuan to interview the award nominee.
- Made a presentation in Legislative Yuan for committee to vote for award winner

Public Health Student Association | *Vice president*

Aug.2018 - Aug.2019

- Engaged in curriculum general meeting and uphold student's right to education
- Organized and negotiated with the school authorities for providing more students space

Public Health Summer Service Team | Leader of Logistics Section

Oct.2018 – Jul.2019

- Raised total \$10,000 USD from Nonprofit Organizations and Foundations.
- Guided 90 students to advocate health promotion in Tainan for a week.

AWARDS

2020	+	Outstanding Graduate Award in College of Public Health, NTU	
2020	•	Nominee of Elite Scholarship of Elite-Well Education Foundation	
2019	•	Nominee of Dr. KP CHEN Memorial Scholarship	
		✓ Dr. KD CHEN is the father of public health in Taiwan, who	

- ✓ Dr. KP CHEN is the father of public health in Taiwan, whose most well-known contribution is to clarify the causality between Blackfoot disease and arsenicosis.
- ✓ Dr. KP CHEN Memorial Scholarship is one of the **Highest award for public health** undergraduates in TAIWAN.

2018 Nominee of Dr. Jiang Jian Memorial Sch	nolarship
---	-----------

2017 • Certificate of Taiwan Medical Information Manager

2017 • Certificate of Complete CITI program in Biomedical Human Subject Research